<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:01:14 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a Penetration Testing Dropbox with Raspberry Pi and OpenVPN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/penetration-testing-dropbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:01:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/penetration-testing-dropbox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As an internal penetration tester, one of the most important aspects of the job is to be able to set up testing infrastructure for remote penetration tests without requiring too much effort from your clients or local IT department.  There seem to be thousands of approaches and an unlimited amount of blog posts online talking about different ways to achieve this objective. The one that seemed the most useful to me was using a public VPN server to connect my workstation with a so-called &amp;ldquo;dropbox&amp;rdquo; in the target&amp;rsquo;s internal network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stepping into the world of OT Penetration Testing with Alchemy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/alchemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 10:54:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/alchemy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After having completed all the previous Pro Labs, I was extraordinarily exited when HackTheBox announced their newest training lab Alchemy. Although originally being exclusive to enterprise users, the lab was released to the public a few months later.  This blog post contains an introduction into the world of operational technology, a review of the Alchemy Pro Lab and an overview of the things I learned while solving it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metamorphic Malware</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/metamorphic-malware/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 17:31:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/metamorphic-malware/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Metamorphic or self-modifying code is an advanced technique used by virus and malware authors which enables their malicious program to rewrite itself in a way that the code remains functionally equivalent but looks different each time it is executed. This characteristic prevents antivirus software from detecting the malware using static signatures and makes reverse engineering more difficult.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High-Level Red Team Training: Cybernetics &amp; APTLabs Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/cybernetics-aptlabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 22:24:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/cybernetics-aptlabs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few months ago, I published a &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/blog/offshore-rastalabs-zephyr&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; where I reviewed the first three HackTheBox Pro Labs that I completed in summer 2023: Offshore, RastaLabs and Zephyr. Over the winter months of this year, I took on the challenge to complete the two remaining advanced labs: Cybernetics and APTLabs. They are both rated as highly challenging, realistic and modern training environments for red team operators and penetration testers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerberos Authentication Protocol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/kerberos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 20:15:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/kerberos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Kerberos protocol provides a single-sign-on (SSO) mutual authentication solution for insecure networks or hosts, where clients and servers verify each others identity based on symmetric-key cryptography and a ticket-based authentication system. Most commonly used in Windows Active Directory environments, a user only has to enter their password once to be able to access a multitude of servers, shares or other resources, while the password is never directly sent across the network, unlike in less secure alternatives like NTLM.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediary-Level Red Team Training: Offshore, RastaLabs &amp; Zephyr Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/offshore-rastalabs-zephyr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 22:07:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/offshore-rastalabs-zephyr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During the summer months of July and August of 2023 I had the opportunity to complete three of the six buyable HackTheBox Pro Lab certifications: Offshore, a Penetration Tester Level 3 lab, as well as RastaLabs and Zephyr, both of which are Red Team Operator Level 1 certifications respectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>